dailydeals.blue 2018-09-07

# Privacy Policy - Daily Deals Blue

This website: **www.dailydeals.blue** (referred to as “Company,” “us,” “we,” and “our”) is committed to respecting your privacy as well as fulfilling our obligations under n the Protection of Individuals with Regard to the Processing of Personal Data and the Free Movement of Such Data.  Therefore, we have created this privacy policy to explain how we use the information that we collect through your use of this Website and to inform you of your rights with regards to this data.   Please read this policy and familiarize yourself with its content as it will govern your use of this site.  **AS A CONDITION OF YOUR CONTINUED USE OF THIS WEBSITE YOU AGREE TO THE FOLLOWING PRIVACY POLICY:**

**Questions**

If you have questions about this policy please contact us by [clicking here](https://dailydeals.blue/contact-us/).

**Non-Personally Identifiable Information**

We may track the Internet Protocol (IP) address which you use to visit this website and analyze this data for trends and statistics, but you will remain anonymous unless you voluntarily provide us with your personally identifiable information.

**Cookies**

We may use cookies on our site in order to improve your browsing experience by personalizing your experience on our site, providing a streamlined sign-up and login process, determining which portions of our site are visited and tailoring advertising to best serve your needs.  Cookies may be placed by an outside company that performs tracking and statistical analysis of visitor behavior pattern, please note that we have no control over third parties and their business practices.

**Collection, Use and Sharing of Personally Identifiable Information**

To access some areas of this website you must first register; such registration will require you to provide personally identifying information.  Whether or not you choose to provide the information we request is entirely up to you.  If you choose not to provide the information which we request, you may be unable to access certain areas of this website or obtain the coupons offered by our site.

If you choose to provide information to us through our online registration, you may be asked to provide your personal information that may include your name, address, telephone number, e-mail address, and other identifying information.   We will not share any personal information which you provide with our third party processing agents, affiliates and advertisers.

We may collect, use and share your personally identifiable information for any lawful purpose.

We will not share any of the data you have entered in this website

By signing up on our website and providing your personal information you are expressly consenting to receive communications from us.  In addition, you expressly consent to be contacted in any manner including via email, direct mail, telephone or SMS text messaging, even if your information is listed on the National Do Not Call registry or a similar registry.  If you do not agree to these terms than do not use our site.

**Opt-Out**

To opt-out of receiving emails from this Website please [click here](https://dailydeals.blue/newsletter-signup/). We will promptly place you on a suppression list for this site and will no longer provide your personally identifiable information to our partners or other third-parties however we cannot stop further communications to you from our partners or other third parties whom we have already provided with your information.  Please note that we may still communicate with you regarding site maintenance, changes to this privacy policy or your account.

**Your Rights to information and Access**

You have the right to be informed of the identity of www.dailydeals.blue. See Accessing and Updating Your Information.  You have the right to be informed of the purpose of the data processing and additional information such as: the categories of recipients of the data, whether the data requested is compulsory, and the consequences of refusal to provide the data.  See Collection Use and Sharing of Personally Identifiable Information.

You have the right to obtain from www.dailydeals.blue, upon a written and signed request, free of charge, once a year, information regarding how your data is being processed by www.dailydeals.blue.   You may designate whether you wish to be informed at a specific address, or email address.  Within 15 days of receipt of this request, www.dailydeals.blue will provide this confirmation along with the following information requested: information regarding the purposes of the data processing, the categories of data processed, the categories of recipients of the data, your rights of intervention and objection, and information concerning the technical principles of the data processing.

**Your Rights to Intervention and Objection**

You have the right to rectify, update, block, delete, or transfer into anonymous form, your personal data.  Such requests can be made free of charge, in writing and signed, to www.dailydeals.blue at any time. www.dailydeals.blue will notify third parties of this request where possible and where notification does not involve disproportionate effort.

You may object at any moment to the processing of your personal data based on justified and legitimate reasons (or where the purpose is for overt marketing), unless there are contrary specific legal provisions.  This request may be made free of charge and at any moment.

You may underline your desire to be informed of the results of an intervention or objection petition at a specific address, or email address. And www.dailydeals.blue will respond within 15 days of receipt of this request

**Accessing and Updating Your Information. Rights of the Data Subject**

To request information regarding your personal data, access your data, or exercise your rights to intervention or objection, please contact us at:

**Daily Deals Blue**  
**Email:** blue@dailydeals.blue

**Third-Party Hosting**

We may contract with a third party to maintain and host the Website and to store data collected on the site. Therefore any information you submit, including personal information, may be placed and stored on a computer server maintained by a third-party host.  You agree that Company is not liable for any breach of security due to the actions or inaction’s of the third-party host.

**Links to Other Websites**

The Website may contain links to other sites.  Any such links are an accommodation to the respective third-party site owners and for your convenience.  Sites linked to and from our Website are not necessarily under the control of Company, and Company shall have no responsibility or liability whatsoever for the content or privacy practices of any linked sites, or any link or linking program at any time.  Please note that other sites will have their own privacy policies which may differ from this policy and once you enter another site their policy will control your use of that site.  We encourage you to read the privacy policy of any site that you visit.

**Security**

This Website has security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse, and alteration of the information under our control.

**Arbitration**

Any and all controversies and disputes arising in connection with use of the Site, these Terms of Use and/or their interpretation shall be settled by arbitration in Bucharest, Romania, by the Court of International Commercial Arbitration of the Romanian Chamber of Commerce and Industry, in compliance with the Rules of Arbitration Procedure of the Court of International Commercial Arbitration, in force, published in the Official Monitor of Romania, Part I, and judgment upon award may be entered in any court having jurisdiction thereof. You agree and submit to the personal jurisdiction and venue of any such court of competent jurisdiction.

**Choice of Law**

The law of Romania, without giving effect to its principles of conflicts of law or the United Nations Convention on Contracts for the International Sale of Goods, shall govern use of the Site, the validity and construction of these Terms of Use, and the interpretation of the rights and duties arising here-under.

**Changes**

We reserve the right to modify the terms of this privacy policy at any time and in our sole discretion, by posting a change notice on this page.  **YOUR CONTINUED USE OF THE WEBSITE FOLLOWING OUR POSTING OF A CHANGE NOTICE WILL CONSTITUTE BINDING ACCEPTANCE OF THOSE CHANGES.**
